I saw this weird vending machine...
Vending machine?
It was just sitting out
at a shut-down love hotel,
and I've never seen that brand before.
That is weird.
And you can't buy anything.
The thing was on so I tried putting
some money in, but it came back.
"Weekly Training Schedule"
"Win the National Tournament"
And it had this weird logo, too.
Shut up, first-years!
She's so scary!
Did you hear? Hikawa isn't going
to qualify for the national tournament.
Oh, wow. Didn't she get accepted
into this school as an athlete?
Piece of shit.
Thank you for finding one of my precious coins.
Please allow me to return the favor.
Get set!
I feel so light! So strong!
Faster!
With these legs, I can go anywhere!
Those little punks can't touch me!
That's it! Faster! Faster!
What the...? What is this?!
Damn it! Where are they?!
I still can't find a single one!
Shit!
By the way, Shuichi. Do you know what this is?
No, I've never seen it. Is it a coin?
It seems to be related
to you monsters somehow...
"You monsters"?
If you don't know, that's fine.
Hang on a sec!
Pathetic!
Come on!
I was only planning
to steal the coin from you, but...
Seeing my face is a problem.
I guess I'll kill you.
Die!
--Excuse me.
--Huh?
Shuichi, do it! Now!
What?!
You bitch! I'll kill you!
What are you doing?! Get rid of her!
Shuichi!
What are you running away for! Fight!
That bitch!
I'll kill her!
You idiot. Why'd you run away?
She was defenseless.
H-How'd you know she was an enemy?
Did you hit your head or something?
I didn't know if she was a monster or a thief,
but if someone shows up barefoot
on your balcony, they're an enemy!
You know what I mean!
You had the pepper spray ready!
You knew something might happen, didn't you?
You were talking about the coin, too!
Something about power?!
Oh, you were listening?
You looked to me like you
were about to pass out.
What is that coin? Where did you get it?
We've got a bigger problem.
That girl wants to kill us.
We saw her face.
She'll probably come to silence us.
You wouldn't like it either, having
someone else know you're a monster.
Well...
That girl seemed used to this kind of thing.
Not only has she seen our faces,
she knows where I live.
Yeah, but killing her...?
Call it a prediction.
But what I can say is that given the situation,
it's up to the two of us
to do something about it.
Do something?
Hmm...
You've got a zipper on your back, don't you?
You didn't know?
Seriously, what am I? This is really--
Hey, Shuichi. This coin means something, right?
Maybe the form you take means something, too.
This form's... meaning?
Don't you want to know what you are?
You should find out what's
inside the zipper, don't you think?
Clair, are you serious?
It's like she said...
With that coin, "in exchange
for power, you lose everything."
It might be inside of you.
Something unknown to you--your true power.
My true power?
Don't you think it's absurd?
For you to have that silly
form for absolutely no reason.
Is it true? Do I really have
some kind of great power?
Okay? I'm going to open it.
It must mean something.
Huh?
What? What's in there?
Nothing. There's nothing in there.
Not even a sign of you.
You're empty.
Empty?
Yeah.
--Forget it, that girl is--
--I don't care!
--What do you mean?!
If we don't do something
about her, we'll be killed!
I don't care anymore.
I have nothing.
I'm empty.
A costume... So that's it!
I think I know what it means.
Shuichi, do you mind if I go inside?
What?!
It's worth giving it a try.
What are you talking about?!
Enter the emptiness, and become one.
That must be what the emptiness means.
I don't think so!
Please. I feel like this will make us one.
Okay.
It's so sticky.
I'm not going to get digested
or something, am I?
I don't know, I can't see it.
Are you ready? I'm going in.
Uh, okay.
Wow, it's so sticky and moist.
Wait, be gentle!
Just relax. Here I go.
I'm going all the way in.
It's so warm and fits just right.
D-Does it hurt?
N-No. You... You're inside of me.
Yes. We are one now.
And... I feel it.
What?
Your hatred...
Your sadness...
I don't have those things.
I can feel it! I feel your heart!
Shuichi! Are you okay?
What happened to you? Something terrible?
What should I do?
It's fine. You don't have to do anything.
It's okay, just calm yourself.
Mmm.
I can sense your feelings, too.
Anger, anxiety...
But you haven't yet realized how strong you are.
I will use that strength. How does that sound?
Okay.
Let's defeat her, together.
Found you!
I'm tired of chasing you shitheads!
Where's the bitch?!
Don't fuck with me!
Is that all you got?!
What's wrong, you little shit?
Where's the bitch?!
Where is she?! Tell me!
Are you okay?
Let me handle moving. You focus
on channeling your strength to me.
G-Got it!
I'm not used to controlling you yet!
Come on! Come on!
You little shit!
Trying to pull me down with you?!
You're just jealous of me!
You have no talent!
Run off and play with the other babies!
You're so weak! You little insect!
Ready to die, little shit?!
Clair...?
Shut up!
It's okay. I will protect you.
Hurry up and die!
C-Clair...?
I think I've got the hang of it.
I had trouble at first, but now...
Let's go, Shuichi!
You...!
Hang on, Clair!
That's it. Like a glove!
Pain.
The ugly sensation of hitting someone.
But I couldn't stop Clair.
Agency over my body
had been taken away.
Completely.
You think you're tough, shithead?!
I'll ask you again. And if you
don't answer, I'll snap your leg.
That voice. You're...
How do you use the coins?
Do you give it to someone?
Or take it somewhere?
You think I'm going to answer you, bitch?
Oh, well. Too bad.
Clair, wait!
Probably should have
been nice and answered, huh?
No. This isn't real.
There's no way I could do this!
I can run. I can still run!
I'm not going to die here!
Sorry. I'm not quite ready to die, either.
Clair, stop!
Clair!
This is a bad dream...
Yeah. The absolute worst nightmare.
It's over. Hey, so actually...
...I kind of pissed myself
while I was inside you.
That was a joke.
A week has passed since that night.
And my routine...
...hasn't changed at all.
Every day I go to school like always,
chat with my friends like always...
It's as if nothing ever happened.
"Clair"
She's in my contacts? When did she do that?!
--Huh?
--What's wrong?
Ooh, did you get a girlfriend?
No! I just don't recognize
the number. It surprised me.
Why don't you answer?
Don't ignore me.
You don't need to come to my classroom.
It's your fault for not picking up.
But the fact that nothing
has happened in the past week
means that nobody found out who we are, right?
That was a crazy experience, though.
When I went inside you...
The sensation of melding with the costume...
The power rising up inside...
The incredible sense of smell...
The pain of being hit...
And sensing your feelings
as though they were mine...
It felt absolutely amazing! How was it for you?
It doesn't bother you?! You killed someone!
I killed her. It's not
your responsibility at all.
Still, it was a legitimate act of self-defense.
Forget it. I don't want anything
to do with you anymore.
If you want to reveal my identity, go ahead.
If you do, I'll tell people what you did.
Can you fight? All by yourself.
There must be more of you. More monsters.
What will you do if another one comes after you?
Can you defend yourself?
It's true. If she hadn't been there,
I would have been killed.
You can't do it. You're too kind.
And I can't defeat a monster
like that with my skinny little arms.
But if the two of us join forces...
...we can take on anyone.
I'm scared. I don't know what's going on.
I don't know how I got like this
or what's going to happen...
If this is some kind of illness,
could I just drop dead?
What if I transform and can't go back?
How will I live?
I didn't know. You're terrified of transforming,
but you still saved me.
You are strong.
To tell the truth,
I don't know why you transform
or whether or not this coin is involved.
Elena... Is that you?
Yes.
So, I can't guarantee you won't die
or keep what you fear from happening.
And things will probably
only get worse from here.
That's why there's one thing I will promise you.
It doesn't matter why...
But if something happens to you,
I'll die with you.
So even if you die, you won't be alone.
We two are one.
What if I say I want to die now?
All right...
Shuichi... I'll be waiting for you!
Too bad. So close to letting it all go.
What the hell are you thinking?
To tell the truth,
I'm looking for my older sister.
Long story short--she's a monster, like you.
Take this for me, Clair.
So... Where is she?
She disappeared.
After killing my mother and father.
What?!
My sister's crime, these monsters...
This town is a real mess.
We were brought together by destiny.
"Hotel Mythos"
"Half a year earlier"
Please, help me find my coins.
As thanks, I will grant any wish you have.
So, can I use my wish on someone else?
Huh? Hmm... I think I can handle that,
but are you sure it's okay?
Forcing your wish on someone else like that.
The truth is...
There's someone I want to be with!
"Episode 3: Elena"